Finding aid for the Hearst Corporation Los Angeles Examiner photographs, negatives and clippings - oversize portrait and subject files 7000.3
USC Libraries Special Collections
- Oversize Portrait Files
  - P-Q
    - Potter -- Miscellaneous (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Powell -- Miscellaneous (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Powell, Dick -- And June Allyson (Box 152, Folder 13-15)
    - Powell, Dick -- Groups (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Powell, Eleanor -- Actress (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Powell, Jane -- Alone (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Powell, Jane -- And Geary Steffen -- And Children (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Powell, Jane -- And Pat Nerney (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Powell, Jane -- Groups (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Powell, William -- Actor (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Power -- Or Powers -- Miscellaneous (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Power, Tyrone (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Powers, Mala (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Pra-Prh (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Presley, Elvis -- Actor (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Preston -- Miscellaneous (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Pri-Prn (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Price -- Miscellaneous (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Price, Vincent -- Actor (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Pro-Prt (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Pu-Pz (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Pullen -- Miscellaneous (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Purcell -- Miscellaneous (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Q (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Quezon -- Miscellaneous (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Quinn -- Miscellaneous (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Quinn, Anthony -- With Wife and Family (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Quirino, Elpidio (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - R
    - Ra-Ral (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Radford, Arthur W. -- Adm. and Mrs. (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Rafferty, Frances -- Actress (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Raft, George (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Ragen -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Raines-Rains -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Raines, Ella (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Ralston, Esther -- Actress (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Ralston, Vera Htuba -- Skater and Actress (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Ram-Raz (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Ramadier, Paul (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Ramsay-Ramsey -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Rand -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Randolph -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Rankin -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Raschi, Vic (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Rasmussen, Gustav (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Rathbone -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Rau, Sir Benegal (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Ray, Aldo (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Ray, Charles (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - Ray, Raye -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Rayburn -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - Raymond -- Miscellaneous (Box 156, Folder 21)
    - Rea-Rec (Box 158, Folder 1-4)
    - Reagan, Ronald -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 158, Folder 9-15)
    - Reardon (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Red-Ree (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Reece -- Miscellaneous (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Reed -- Miscellaneous (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Reed, Donna -- Actress (Box 157, Folder 4-7)
    - Reed, Donna -- And Husband (Tony Owen) (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Reeves -- Miscellaneous (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Ref-Reh (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Rei (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Reid -- Miscellaneous (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Reilly -- Miscellaneous (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Reiser -- Miscellaneous (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Rej-Reo (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Remington, William (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Rennie, Michael -- And Wife (Margaret McGrath) (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Rep-Rh (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Reuther -- Miscellaneous (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Reynolds -- Miscellaneous (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Reynolds, Allie (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Reynolds, Debbie (Box 157, Folder 17-20)
    - Reynolds, Joyce (Box 157, Folder 21)
    - Reynolds, Marjorie -- Actress (Box 157, Folder 22)
    - Reynolds, Milton (Box 157, Folder 23)
    - Rhee, Syngman, Dr. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Ria-Rib (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Ric-Ricz (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Rice -- Miscellaneous (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Rich -- Miscellaneous (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - Rich, Irene -- Actress (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - Rich, Lillian -- Actress (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - Richard -- Miscellaneous (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - Richards -- Miscellaneous (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Richardson -- Miscellaneous (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Richardson, James O. -- Admiral (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Richter -- Miscellaneous (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Rickenbacker -- Miscellaneous (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Rickey -- Miscellaneous (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Rid-Rie (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Ridgeway -- Miscellaneous (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Ridgway, Matthew B., General (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Rif-Rig (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Rih-Rim (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Riley -- Miscellaneous (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Rin (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Ringberg, Kirsten (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Rio-Rir (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Ris (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Rit (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Ritchie, Betty (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Ritz -- Miscellaneous (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Riu-Rn (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Rizzuto, Phil (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Roa-Rob (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Roach -- Miscellaneous (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Robb, Inez -- Writer (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Robbins -- Miscellaneous (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Robbins, Gale -- Actress (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Roberts -- Miscellaneous (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Roberts, Edith -- Actress -- 1922 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Robertson -- Miscellaneous (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Robertson, Dale (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Robeson, Paul -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Robinson -- Miscellaneous (Box 162, Folder 1-4)
    - Robinson, Edward G. -- Actor (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Robinson, Jackie (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Robinson, Ray "Sugar" -- And Wife (Box 162, Folder 6-10)
    - Robson, May -- Actress (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Roc (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Rocco -- Miscellaneous (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller -- Miscellaneous (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop -- And Wife (Box 162, Folder 15-16)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop -- Mr. and Mrs. (Barbara) (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Rockwell -- Miscellaneous (Box 162, Folder 18)
    - Rod (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Rodriguez -- Miscellaneous (Box 162, Folder 19)
    - Roe-Rog (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Rogers -- Miscellaneous (Box 162, Folder 20)
    - Rogers, Charles "Buddy" (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Rogers, Edith Nourse (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Rogers, Ginger -- Actress (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Rogers, Roy (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Rogers, William P. (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Rogge, O. John (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Roh-Rol (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Rom (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Roman -- Miscellaneous (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Roman, Ruth (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Romania -- Royalty (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Romanoff -- Or Romanov -- Miscellaneous (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Romay, Lina (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Romero -- Miscellaneous (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Romero, Cesar (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Romulo, Carlos, General (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Ron-Ror (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Rooney -- Miscellaneous (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - Rooney, Mickey -- Actor (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor -- Mrs. (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt, Elliot -- And Wife (Fae Emerson) (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D. Jr. (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President -- Alone (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President -- Family (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President -- Funeral (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President -- Home -- All pictures Without Him (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President -- Large Groups (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President -- Small Groups (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Roosevelt, James -- And Wife (Romelle) (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, President (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Rosa-Roz (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Rose -- Miscellaneous (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Rosenberg -- Miscellaneous (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Rosenberg, Julius and Ethel (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Ross -- Miscellaneous (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Ross, Barney (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Ross, Charles (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Ross, Mae -- Ice skater (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Rossellini -- Miscellaneous (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Rosso -- Miscellaneous (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Roth -- Miscellaneous (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Rowe -- Miscellaneous (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Rowland -- Miscellaneous (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Royall -- Miscellaneous (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Royall, Kenneth (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Ru-Rz (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Rubin -- Miscellaneous (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Ruggles -- Miscellaneous (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Ruick, Barbara (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Ruiz Cortines, Adolf -- Mexico President -- 1952 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Runyon -- Miscellaneous (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Rupp, William Jr. -- Sex Slayer (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Rush, Barbara -- Actress (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Russell -- Miscellaneous (Box 167, Folder 8-10)
    - Russell, Gail (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Russell, Jane -- Actress (Box 167, Folder 11-12)
    - Russell, Rosalind -- Actress (Box 167, Folder 13-16)
    - Ruth, Babe (Box 168, Folder 2-5)
    - Rutherford, Ann -- Actress (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Rutledge -- Miscellaneous (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Ryan -- Miscellaneous (Box 168, Folder 8-9)
    - Ryan, Peggy (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Ryan, Robert -- Actor -- And Wife (Jessica) (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Ryan, Sheila -- Actress (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - S
    - Sa-Sad (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Sae-Sai (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Saj-Sam (Box 169, Folder 1-5)
    - Salk, Jones E., Doctor (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - San (Box 169, Folder 7-8)
    - San Juan, Olga (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Sander, Herman, Doctor (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Sanders -- Miscellaneous (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Sanders, George (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Sanford, Laddie (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Sao-Sas (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Sat (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Sau-Saz (Box 169, Folder 16-18)
    - Saunders -- Miscellaneous (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Sawyer, Eddie (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Sayre, Francis B. (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Sca-Scha (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Sche (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Schildkraut, Joseph (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Schlacht -- Miscellaneous (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Schmidt -- Miscellaneous (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Schmidt, Patricia (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Schn-Schr (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Schnedorf, Jerome, Doctor -- And Family (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Schneider -- Miscellaneous (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Schroeder -- Miscellaneous (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Schroeder, Ted (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Schs-Schz (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Schuman -- Miscellaneous (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Schwartz -- Miscellaneous (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Schwellenbach, Lewis B. (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Sci-Scz (Box 171, Folder 10-13)
    - Scott -- Miscellaneous (Box 171, Folder 14-16)
    - Scott, Adrian (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Scott, Barbara Ann -- Skater (Box 171, Folder 18)
    - Scott, Joe -- Attorney (Box 171, Folder 19)
    - Scott, Joseph, Judge -- Obituary -- December 4, 1952 (Box 171, Folder 20)
    - Scott, Lewing (Box 171, Folder 21)
    - Scott, Lizabeth (Box 171, Folder 22)
    - Scott, Randolph (Box 171, Folder 23)
    - Scott, Zachary -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Sd-Sg (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Se-Sg (Box 172, Folder 15-22)
    - Sears -- Miscellaneous (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Sebald -- Miscellaneous (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Sebastian, Dorothy -- Actress -- 1928 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Sedgman, Frank (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Seely, Blossom -- Actress -- 1933 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Segovia -- Duke and Duchess (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Sellers -- Miscellaneous (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Seminick, Andy (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Service -- Miscellaneous (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Seven, Toni -- Actress (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Sewell -- Miscellaneous (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Seymour -- Miscellaneous (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Sforza, Carlos (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Sha-Shd (Box 173, Folder 1-5)
    - Shafer -- Miscellaneous (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Shannon -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Shapiro -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Sharpe (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Shaw -- Miscellaneous (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Shaw, George Bernard (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - She- (Box 173, Folder 8-12)
    - Shea -- Miscellaneous (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - Shearer -- Miscellaneous (Box 173, Folder 18)
    - Shearer, Norma (Box 173, Folder 19)
    - Shelter -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - Shelton -- Miscellaneous (Box 173, Folder 20)
    - Shepard and Sheppard -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Sher -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Sheridan, Ann -- Actress (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Sherman -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Sherman, Forrest P., Admiral -- Died July 22, 1951 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Sherry -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Sherwood -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - Shi-Shn (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Shields -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - Shigemitsu, Mamoru (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Shirley, Ann -- Actress (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - Sho-Sht (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Shopp, Bebe (Box 174, Folder 19)
    - Shore, Dinah -- Singer (Box 175, Folder 1-4)
    - Short -- Miscellaneous (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Short, Walter C., Major General (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Shostakovitch, Dmitri (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Shotton, Burt (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Shu-shz (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Si (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Siam -- Royalty (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Sidney, Sylvia -- Actress (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Sigler -- Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Silver-Silvers -- Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Simmons -- Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Simmons, Jean (Box 176, Folder 4-5)
    - Simms, Ginny -- Singer (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Simon -- Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Simpson -- Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Sinatra, Frank -- Singer (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Singleton -- Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Sink, Roland -- Runner (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Sinkwich, Frankie -- Football (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Sisler, Dick (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Sissell, Martha -- Rose Queen of 1962 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Sj-Sk (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Skelton -- Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - Skelton, Richard "Red" (Box 176, Folder 16-19)
    - Skinner -- Miscellaneous (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - Sl (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Slater -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Slaughter -- Miscellaneous (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Slezak, Walter -- Actor (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Sm-sn (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Smead, Frederick, Sergeant (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Smigelski, Fred W. -- Boy Murderer (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Smith, A-M (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Alexis -- Actress (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Alfred E. (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Smith, B -- Miscellaneous (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Colin (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Smith, D -- Miscellaneous (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Smith, E -- Miscellaneous (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Forrest (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Gerald L. K. (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Smith, H -- Miscellaneous (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Smith, H. Alexander (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Smith, J -- Miscellaneous (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Smith, J. Kingsbury (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Smith, James -- Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Smith, John -- Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Joseph -- Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Smith, L -- Miscellaneous (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Margaret Chase (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Smith, N-Z (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Smith, R -- Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Richard -- Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Robert -- Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Smith, V -- Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - Smith, W -- Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Walter Bedell, Lieutenant General (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Snead -- Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 20)
    - Snead, Sam -- Golf Champion (Box 178, Folder 21)
    - Snider, Duke (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Snite, Fred Jr. (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Snow -- Miscellaneous (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Snyder -- Miscellaneous (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Soa-Soz (Box 179, Folder 5-11)
    - Solomon -- Miscellaneous (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - Sonnett -- Miscellaneous (Box 179, Folder 13)
    - Sothern, Ann -- Actress (Box 179, Folder 14)
    - Spa-Sr (Box 180, Folder 1-7)
    - Spaatz, Carl A., General (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Spain -- Royalty (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Sparkman, John J., Senator -- And Family (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Spellman -- Miscellaneous (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Spence -- Miscelleneous (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - St. Laurent, Louis (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - St., A-Z (Box 169, Folder 12-14)
    - Sta-Stz (Box 180, Folder 13-19)
    - Stack -- Miscellaneous (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Stack, Robert (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Stagg, Amos Alonzo (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Stalin, Josef (Box 181, Folder 4 - 7)
    - Stanley -- Miscellaneous (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Stanton -- Miscellaneous (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Stanwyck, Barbara -- Actress (Box 181, Folder 10 - 14)
    - Stark-Starks -- Miscellaneous (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - Starke, Pauline -- Actress (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - Starr -- Miscellaneous (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - Stassen -- Miscellaneous (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - Stassen, Harold E. (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - Ste (Box 181, Folder 20 - 24)
    - Steel-Steele (Box 181, Folder 25)
    - Steelman -- Miscellaneous (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Stein -- Miscellaneous (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Sten, Anna -- Actress (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Stengel, Casey (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Stephan -- Miscellaneous (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Stephens -- Miscellaneous (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Stephenson -- Miscellaneous (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Sterling -- Miscellaneous (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Sterling, Ann (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Sterling, Jan -- Actress (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Sterling, Robert -- Actor (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - Stern -- Miscellaneous (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - Stettinius, Edward R. -- And Wife (Box 182, Folder 13)
    - Stevens -- Miscellaneous (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Stevens, Craig (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Stevens, Dorothy Mae -- Frozen Woman (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Stevens, K. T. (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Stevens, Mark (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, Rise -- Singer (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Stevenson -- Miscellaneous (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Stevenson, Adlai -- California Visit (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Stevenson, Adlai -- Governor of Illinois (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Stewart -- Miscellaneous (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Stewart, Elaine -- Actress (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Stewart, James -- Actor (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Sti (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Stillwell -- Miscellaneous (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Sto (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Stoddard, Alexander J. (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Stokowski -- Miscellaneous (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Stompanato, Johnny -- Cohen-ite -- Stabbed to Death by Lana Turner's Daughter (Cheryl Crane) (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Stone -- Miscellaneous (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Storey-Story -- Miscellaneous (Box 184, Folder 8-9)
    - Storm, Gale -- Actress (Box 184, Folder 10-12)
    - Str-sty (Box 184, Folder 11-21)
    - Stranahan, Frank -- Golf (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Street -- Miscellaneous (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Stribling, Robert -- Writer (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Stripling -- Miscellaneous (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Stritch, Samuel A. -- Cardinal (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Stroble, Fred (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Stuart -- Miscellaneous (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Stuart, Gloria -- Actress (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Styles, Harry J. (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Su-Sv (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Sullavan, Margaret -- Actress (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Sullivan -- Miscellaneous (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Sullivan, Barry (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Sullivan, John L., Navy Secretary (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Sutton -- Miscellaneous (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Sutton, John (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Sw-Sy (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - Swan -- Miscellaneous (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Swancutt, Woodrow P. -- Dropped Atomic Bomb (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Swanson -- Miscellaneous (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Swanson, Gloria -- Actress (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - Sweden -- Royalty (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - Sweet, Blanche -- Actress -- 1923 (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Swope -- Miscellaneous (Box 186, Folder 13)
    - Symington, W. Stuart (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Sz (Box 186, Folder 14)
  - T, U, V
    - T-Tg (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Tab-Tay (Box 187, Folder 2-9)
    - Taft, Robert A., Senator (Box 187, Folder 10-13)
    - Talmadge -- Miscellaneous (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Talmadge, Norma -- Actress (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Taylor -- Miscellaneous (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Don (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Elizabeth -- Alone (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Taylor, Elizabeth -- Groups (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Taylor, Estelle -- Actress (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Glen H. (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - Taylor, Maxwell D., General (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - Taylor, Robert -- Actor (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - Temple, Shirley -- Alone (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Temple, Shirley -- Groups (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Terry -- Miscellaneous (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Th-Thz (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Thiess, Ursula -- Actress (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Thomas -- A-D (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Thomas -- E (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Thomas -- F-I (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Thomas -- J-O (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Thomas -- P-Z (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, Danny -- Actor (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Thomas, J. Parnell (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Thompson -- Miscellaneous (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Thompson, Marshall (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Thompson, Melvin E., Governor (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Thompson, William "Red" (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Thomson, Bobby (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - Thorne -- Miscellaneous (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - Tibbett, Lawrence -- And Mrs. (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - Tibbetts -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Tierney -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - Tierney, Gene (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Titus, Lola (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - To-Toz (Box 192, Folder 1-6)
    - Tobey -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - Tobias -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 12)
    - Tobin -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 13)
    - Todd -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 14)
    - Togliatti, Palmiro (Box 192, Folder 15)
    - Toguri, Iva (Box 192, Folder 16)
    - Tolstoy -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 17)
    - Tone, Franchot (Box 192, Folder 18)
    - Tongay -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 19)
    - Toomey -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 20)
    - Topping -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 21)
    - Toren, Marta (Box 192, Folder 22)
    - Torlonia -- Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 23)
    - Torme, Mel -- And wife (Box 192, Folder 24)
    - Torres -- Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Torresola -- Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Toscanini, Arturo (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Totter, Audrey -- Actress (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Townsend -- Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Townsend, Colleen (Box 191, Folder 6-7)
    - Tr-Tz (Box 191, Folder 8-15)
    - Tracy -- Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 16)
    - Tracy, Spencer -- And Wife (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - Travis -- Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 11)